

UI/UX Designer

(240)-665-0131 jokouakou@gmail.com 🔽 Philadelphia, PA 19104 jovankouakou.com

Dedicated to my craft, I design beautifully functional interfaces and experiences for web and games with a vast array of skills. In my experience, my diverse talent and ever-growing knowledge base has aided me in my mission to "delight in design".

EDUCATION

Drexel University BACHELOR'S OF SCIENCE COMPUTER SCIENCE GAME DEVELOPMENT CONCENTRATION December 2023

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

3D MODELING ART DIRECTION GAME UI/UX INFORMATION ARCHITECTURE INTERACTION DESIGN **PROTOTYPING USABILITY TESTING** WEB DESIGN WIREFRAMING

SOFTWARE

AFTER EFFECTS, BLAZOR, C#, CSS, FIGMA, HTML, ILLUSTRATOR, INDESIGN, JAVA, JAVASCRIPT, JSON, MAYA, PHOTOSHOP, PREMIERE PYTHON, REACT, SUBSTANCE PAINTER, SQL, TAILWINDCSS, UNREAL, UNITY, WORDPRESS, **WWISE**

INVOLVMENT

MARKETING OFFICER DREXEL GAMING ASSOCIATION

2018-2023

I.T. SUPPORT **GATHER PLACE** NON-PROFIT

2021-2022

FLOOR STAFF NOURISH NOW NON-PROFIT

2017

BUILDER

HABITAT FOR HUMANITY NON-PROFIT 2017

EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC & WEB DESIGNER

Beyond Indigo Pets | April 2024 - Present

Communicated with project manager to establish client needs. Executed on brand strategy to deliver 3 initial logo concepts. Provided clarity within design presentations and received feedback to further develop logos. Produced and delivered final logo and brand package to client.

ONSITE SEO ASSOCIATE

Majux Marketing | February 2024 - Present

Utilized Semrush, Screaming Frog, and Sitebulb auditing platforms to diagnose and fix issues with client websites. Coordinated to resolve problems the sites had to boost client page-rank, click-through rate, and increase leads. Performed qualitative and quantitative research on competitors to create a more effective SEO strategy.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Freelance | September 2022 - Present

Completed 8 projects for web application prototypes, websites, album art, and other graphic design and consulting work. Designed and created portfolio website using React, Framer Motion, and TailwindCSS.

WEB APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER

WellNet Healthcare | September 2021 - March 2022

Responsible for mockup, prototype, and implementation of web application ports of in-house applications by use of Adobe XD, Blazor, and MudBlazor to increase efficiency and output of sales force.

I.T. SUPPORT TECHNICIAN

American Board of Surgery | September 2020 - March 2021

Fielded hundreds of technical and financial tickets on Jira using SQL. Provided timely correspondence with medical professionals on their service status. Provided live technical support to staff and surgeons for national board exams on Zoom.

PROJECTS

AUDIO DESIGNER & ENGINEER

FIRMWARE INFIRMARY | September 2022 - June 2023

Collaborated within a team of 12 seniors to develop a narrative-based game in Unity over the course of 9 months. Updated design documents, composed and implemented original music and sound effects, and integrated dialogue system with audio using a state machine.

UI/UX DESIGNER

SCIRECT | September 2022 - December 2022

Led a team of 4 to perform ideation, qualitative research, wireframe, mockup, and prototype a VR/AR lab application and platform to improve the engagement and accessibility of lab sciences in high schools.